I live here in Nashville I want to tell
you where I'm usually at I was in
Northern Indiana a couple weeks ago not
doing comedy just
sightseeing and I drove I drove past to
prison there I wasn't going to prison I
didn't know there was a prison around
until I saw a sign this is a real sign
out of nowhere medium security prison
nearby do not pick up
hitchhikers okay I've never been in
charge of security at a prison but that
sign does feel like they're saying
look they're getting out all right
and it's happened a bunch it's happening
right now we don't know what to do we're
only a medium security prison why don't
we put it on y'all a little bit stop
picking them up every time let them walk
we're in Northern Indiana they're not
going anywhere right let them get
tuckered out
and they by the way no phone number to
call if you see a hitchhiker no followup
instructions they're just like stay
vigilant cuz they
[Music]
[Applause]
are all
right that's honestly too much that's
honestly yeah yeah it's thank y'all for
being here man what a night happy to be
here in Nashville man happy to be I
never know what to wear on stage I I
overthink it a lot I was looking at my
closet I have two sections in my closet
I have the clothes that kind of
fit and then I have the clothes that you
know one day
might and you know if I wake up and
everything's different I'll be good to
go I just leave them in there for hope I
have all these shirts that I really like
that don't button the way I'd like them
to so I never wear them I said to my
wife I I told her that and she goes you
know you don't have to button the
shirt
so it's been a good year I mean I I
doubled my wardrobe immediately I didn't
I didn't know you were allowed to do
this this is crazy if I find out you
don't have to zip up pants it's over
dude I'll never buy clothes again I I've
been married 3 years now and I love
being married when I'm on the road I see
men talk to women in the wild and it's
crazy I was checking in at a hotel woman
behind the counter very pretty and the
guy in front of me is being a creep I'm
watching him I'm 20 feet behind him but
I can hear it go down right he's
checking in and and the woman goes do
you have any preference of what floor
you stay on and I swear to y'all this
guy leans forward he goes what floor are
you staying
on she goes I'm
not I work here I don't stay at the
hotel that I work do you think I'm a
guest just chipping in down here in the
lobby is that honestly how you think we
staff this laquina you think you got to
be the Lifeguard tomorrow I don't stay
at the hotel that employs me you
so he walks away tail between his legs
rightfully so now I'm up next right I
saw the whole thing go down so I was
like okay I'll bond with her over what a
creep the last dude was so I'm checking
in and she said says how many room keys
do you want one or two so I go how many
room keys do you want and
she she did not get the reference at all
dude I I looked way worse than the first
guy if I'm being honest the look on her
face she's like they just keep coming in
today I mean is there a creep convention
in town what's Happening Here I feel
good though man I i' had been sick for a
while I came down with something I was
sick for like 2 weeks I had to go to
Earth Urgent Care here in Nashville I
don't know if y'all been to an Urgent
Care go check it out it's fun I like it
in there there's a you it's better than
a real doctor I
think there's no ego at an urgent care
that's what's fun you know nobody in an
Urgent Care is like this is where I
thought my life would be and I like that
that's actually a good feeling you go to
a doctor's office they talk down to you
right diplomas on the wall they're like
I went to school I know everything
Urgent Care is is like do you have $40
let's figure this out together we don't
know any more than you you know let's
put our heads in a
room and let's tackle this sinus
infection as a team and that's fun
there's camaraderie in an urgent care
you know I don't know if anybody's
qualified that's a
rush that's a fun way to spend a day you
know how you fill out all your info in
the lobby on like a clipboard and then
they take you to another room and act
like you never did that so the nurse
comes in we're face to face she's asking
me question she goes what are you in for
I said my nose is
clogged she said you've been taking
anything I said just suda fed and she
goes oh can you spell that for
me I was like suda
fed yeah maybe
could
uh I would like you to take a stab at it
though
right feels like something you should
know
I know y'all share a lease with a
T-Mobile store but this feels like day
one stuff
honestly look I've been taking IU profen
as well so
maybe I sounded that one
out you can write that down
phonetically I'm being mean but they
hook me up they gave me a steroid shot I
don't know if you've had a steroid shot
they are awesome I don't know what's in
them it worked work so quick I don't
know why they've been hiding these they
should do a lot more steroid shots that
should be the first thing they throw at
you when you walk in you know just go
around the waiting room just give
everybody a steroid shot and be like
we'll see who needs to be here in 5
minutes most of y'all be feeling better
than you've ever felt in your
life they got me I felt good right away
I had some other medicine I had to get I
don't even know what I had to go to the
pharmacy to get it they didn't have it
urgent care I had to go to a pharmacy
another place across town I know that's
how it works but I don't know why we're
all okay with it you know there's plenty
of room just keep it there why do I got
to go off
campus to get the med you know no other
industry in America works like that can
you imagine you go to Jiffy Lube and
they're like you need a oil
change we don't have any oil here but uh
if you take this piece of paper to
Walgreens they'll get they'll get you
oil in about an hour you know you'll see
it immediately but it'll be an hour
before they turn around and hand it to
you you ever see your NE your bag over
their shoulder you're like can I just
reach out and grab that real quick it's
going to be an hour so I was in there a
while she goes it's going to be about an
hour feel free to walk around our store
I was like really are you sure thank
you you ever walk around a pharmacy
indefinitely there's weird weird stuff
in there there's aisles none of us go to
cuz they're not on the way to anything
fun go check them out there's cool I
bought a knee
brace I didn't know you were allowed to
get a knee brace off the rack 29 bucks
it's pretty good I don't need a knee
brace right now but y'all y'all see me
it's coming I'd like to I want to have a
starter when that day comes
right Breathe Right Strips I was trying
those out big advocate of those you know
a breae Right strip little sticker that
you put on your nose and it just it's uh
even if you're breathing
good you could be breathing a little
better you ever throw on a Breathe Right
strip just to power through the last few
bites of a meal y'all know what I'm
talking about just open things up some
of y'all never breathed I can tell you
don't even know what I'm talking about
you're living life at 60% knows you
could get to
63 I wear them all the time only at home
though that's a home thing isn't it some
things are home
things I thought that would sound more
profound than it did but
uh I saw a friend from high school at
the grocery store I hadn't seen him in
15 years we caught up good conversation
I get back to my car I adjust the rear
view mirror I see myself I had two
Breath Right Strips on my nose that I
had forgotten about he didn't bring it
up a single time he he did ask how I was
doing a lot you sure you're all right
I'm doing great actually just two brief
right STR crisscrossed on my nose which
I do recommend if you do want to double
up you want a crisscross to maximize
the could be these Health Trends I can't
keep up I have friends taking cold
showers now anybody here do that take
cold showers yeah I don't they have hot
water they choose to go cold my buddy's
very into it he goes you know what it is
dude it's a mental thing that's what it
is man it's it's a little hurdle you got
to jump dude when's the last time you
woke up and did something you don't want
to do that's what it is about doing
something you don't want to do when's
the last time you had you did something
that you don't want to do I was like I'm
having this conversation right now but I
said I'll try it I tried a cold shower
it was not long it was the shortest
shower of my life I went back to my
friend I said I can't do a cold shower
man he goes well your mind is
weak I hate to tell you that dude if you
can't do a cold shower you got a weak
mind I was like man I think my mind's
the
strongest cuz I can't convince
it we need to do this right I'm in the
shower I make it cold my brain's like
dude nobody's in here checking on this
just lie and say you did it later I'm
like that's a pretty good point I will
do
that so I'm not doing cold shower I do
take care of myself I try I've been
trying I eat a lot of
Tums those Tums are very good I don't
know if you've had Tums lately they've
gotten last 10 years have been special
it's borderline top five candy in the
country right now I give it out on
Halloween it's gotten so good they just
came out with orange cream I don't know
if y'all get the same email as I do but
new flavor just
dropped it's orange cream Tums half of
them are orange half of them are
cream and then you can kind of mix and
mat that's what Toms does they let you
decide you know how strong do you want
to go right you can go all orange today
live it up but at some point you got to
go all
cream is this relatable what I do I got
a system I do two orange one cream I put
some M&M's in there I shake it up it's
good it's tearing me up but I'm enjoying
the ride
and they could have made Tums a pill
remember that you know there are antd
pills Tums could have been a pill but
they were like nah our customers are
going to want to choose something so we
might as well make it delicious which
which they did and I appreciate that you
know go get some tonight if you don't
believe me good gas stations got it I
love a good gas station there's a great
gas station by my house I'm in there all
the time I talk to the employees they
know me this just happened I was in
there I had a weird thing with the woman
the cashier I bought a beer at the gas
station and the cashier goes when's your
birthday honey and I said November 13
1991 and she goes oh my daughter is on
the 1 but you know different
year so you're telling me nothing is
that what I said three things and two of
them don't apply to your daughter who
I've never met what do you want me to
say to that get her in here dude I got
are you kidding me I got to meet this
girl November what that's insane get her
in here I didn't know I didn't know what
to say I just said it's a good month
that's what I said it's a good month and
I've been thinking about her ever since
I'll be honest how often is she saying
this to people is it one out of every 12
customers that come in she's like I'm
about to blow your mind you know my
daughter who you don't know same
[Music]
month different year you can get a good
hot dog at a gas station occasionally
I'll try a hot dog anywhere I had the
best hot dog of my life you'll never
guess where Seattle Washington anybody
from anybody heard of it um it's a big
city I went to a baseball game out there
I left the Stadium there's a hot dog
stand right outside so I walk up I said
I would like a hot dog and the guy goes
what do you want on it and I was just in
a you know I wasn't ready to answer that
so I was uh do it I I told the guy to do
it and he looked like he been ready for
somebody to say that he goes my friend I
got you and I watch him he takes the hot
dog bun this guy starts putting cream
cheese on the bun I was like you're
crazy hey why do you have that back
there that's not even a hot dog
ingredient did you bring that from home
you can't use home stuff at a restaur
some things are home things remember
that was that worth it
nope all
right he goes my friend trust me and
then he takes he starts putting brown
onions on top of that hot dog I go
there's no way this is good it was the
best hot dog I've ever had I've thought
about it all the time I think about it
all the time I've told a lot of people
about this hot dog I've evangelized this
place all over North America if I find
out you're going to Seattle I'll send
you the
coordinates of this hot dog stand that's
the impact it's had on me anyway the
whole reason I bring that up is because
a few months ago this is two years later
I'm back in Seattle I went to another
baseball game I didn't care about the
game I left in the second inning I'm
trying to find that hot dog stand right
and it's in the same spot and I walk up
I promise y'all same day dude from two
years ago I'll never forget his
eyes and I look right at him I go hey
dude you're not going to remember
me it is a big day for
me I've been thinking about you for two
years you you changed my life in 2021
you won't remember this I came in I
think I was in a mood maybe you were in
a mood I don't know I said do
it you did it you put cream jeez on a
hot dog but I've never seen that before
in my life could you do that for me
again he looks at me all weird he goes
my friend are you talking about the
Seattle
dog and he points at the menu above his
head I didn't see the menu two years ago
there's one item on the menu of this hot
dog stand it's the Seattle Dog a hot dog
with you guessed it cream cheese and
grilled onions it's the only thing this
guy makes he makes one item all day
every day I've talked about it for 2
years like he invented it for me it's
the signature hot dog of the city I've
recommended it to people from Seattle do
you know how stupid that makes me look
to recommend the signature dish in that
City that's like if I went to
Philadelphia and I was like Yo dude I
found this spot today y'all should check
out this dude put cheese on a steak
sandwich I know I know it sounds crazy
just tell him I sent you he'll do it
he'll hook it
up I
shouldn't be having hot dogs I'm 32
years old relatively healthy just had
that confirmed at urgent care
but I have things I'm too young to have
I have sleep AB yet I got to wear a cat
machine to
thanks we got to stick together out here
man I clocked you when you walked in
I'll say that I knew I had some kin folk
out
here these people don't get it man we
got to plug into a wall to
sleep think about that we need
electricity to
dream there's stuff you can't do right
my buddy invited me camping he's like
you want to come on a camping trip I was
like do you want to carry a car battery
through the woods cuz I need an
outlet when I got diagnosed I had to go
to a sleep doctor he told me Aaron don't
worry sleep apnea is not always weight
related oh neat uh is it weight related
for me for sure but uh yeah I'm just
saying I thought you'd find it
cool not everybody earned it I'm not
embarrassed I don't care I'm 32 I'm
married I'm not trying to impress y'all
I'm trying to
breathe I don't even know if it's my
fault they say head size is an indicator
if you have a big head you probably have
sleep apnea
so yeah y'all don't have to look around
right now but at some point tonight peek
around your
table you know I walked in the sleep
doctor's office I got a big head he sees
me he goes bingo I was like on dude let
my head is Big this how big my head is
if I like to I like to wear a hat I like
to wear a baseball hat there's only one
brand of hat that fits my head it's a
new era 5950 snapback hat youall know
Snapback at snaps in the
back on a good head day I could maybe
get one button to snap and it doesn't
want a button dude it's like I'll click
on there I'm not going to be good and it
just and it hurts and I I got to take it
off when I
eat cuz if I if I get chewing too
hard you ever see a big dude walking
around his hatch just blown out in the
back let that guy live his life dude he
feels the wind blowing on his neck he
knows what's
happening but I got to get it together
the big reason is any day now my wife
and I are going to have our first baby
which is very exciting any day
now it's a girl we we found out it's a
girl we saw an ultrasound today actually
it's pretty CRA that kid's coming
in it's starting to show up I know that
sounds stupid but the first ultrasound
is pretty weak I think they they do it
too early I you know I lied and said I
saw
it I didn't want to be the only one in
the room that couldn't see you know the
whole room's ooing and on I'm like
I all right call her up you nurse goes
she's waving at you she's
waving is this one of those 3D where you
have to back up and then it shows up
finally I go oh man she's
gorgeous and then I was driving home I
said to my wife I got a level with you I
didn't see a thing on that screen she
goes me either okay cool glad we printed
it
out just send a blob to the family here
is it's coming in now though man she's
got toes it's pretty crazy we're moving
right now that's the big project we're
moving to a bigger house we got a
realtor to sell our old house she told
us we got to get our house
livable I've lived there for
years she's like we got to get it to
where a person would want to be in
here I get it but oh God that
hurts I'm not going to miss our
neighbors I've never talked to the
neighbors is that weird y'all hang out
with your neighbors a lot they close her
blinds pretty quick and I respect that
you know my wife wants me to meet him so
she's at work this is a few weeks ago
I'm taking out the trash the guy next
door to me I assume he lives there too
he's taking out his trash so I was like
there he is so I go I go hey what's up
man' he goes how about
it so we
met one of the better conversations I've
ever had in my life so my wife gets home
and I said I met the neighbor today and
she goes oh my God what's his name I
don't know but I love
him she goes what does he do takes his
trash out on time I know that she goes
did he buy the house or is he renting it
I go how do you think this conversation
went I don't know his name or his
occupation how insane would it be if I
did know that how do you think I meet
people in the world every day what's
going on man how are you you got a
mortgage Let's uh let's get right into
it you know I'm trying to fix the house
I'm trying I can't do anything around
the house I can't do it I don't even
know the words to talk to a guy who can
fix the house I had a plumbing issue in
my basement my wall was
bleeding that's how I said it I I
couldn't think of the word
leak I was in my basement for an hour
going it's bleeding Hard Out Here we
need we need a
tet I don't know any words so I call the
plum he goes I'll be out there in a gif
now I'm not trashing plumbers but y'all
know what a gif means 19 hours it's is
fine lot of stuff to Plum I'm not mad at
him right but by the time this guy gets
to my house it had been so long the leak
had stopped I don't know what happened I
didn't do anything it just you know
scabbed
up it's just fine and I've been mopping
up the floor so it kind of looks fine uh
in the basement so now I'm trying to
convince this dude I didn't make the
whole thing up he walks down my basement
he goes I see what you're talking
about all right cool yeah yeah you mind
poking around a little bit first before
you just write it off you know and then
he starts knocking on the wall starts
scratching it he goes
solid I go cool did you think I just
wanted to hang out with you in my house
today I didn't make this up right now
we're just two men looking at each
other in my basement it's kind of an
awkward Ward impass between two adult
men that you know I'll be honest look a
lot
alike finally he broke he goes I hear
you dude all right I hear you why don't
I do this I got saw in my truck I'll
come down here I'll cut a little hole in
this drywall and
I'll and I need y'all to know before I
finish the story deep down I know that
dry wall is a typee of
wall I don't know if I could pick it out
of a lineup of walls but I've I've heard
people talk about wall drywall before
deep down I know drywall exists I wasn't
reaching too deep in the moment though I
heard drywall I thought this guy was
mocking
me to my fa I thought he was like you
thought you had a leak why don't we look
at this dry wall I was like it was wet
this morning dude about a gif ago it was
a nightmare down here
so he cut a giant hole and then he just
left I go you mind unho holding the wall
this was your idea dude patch it up you
go you can probably patch that up I like
I'm going have to get a new house I
don't even know what you're talking
about patch it up with what I got walls
laying around thing what are you talking
about I don't even know conceptually
what you're asking me to I go get a wall
cool Home Depot one wall please please
again some good
tape the big project now this has been
like a 2-year Saga as I have a shed and
I don't do a lot of shed stuff so these
raccoons kind of took it
over and they're just they're just in
there and I got to get rid of them I
don't want to kill them you know I want
them to
die so don't be fooled by a raccoon I
can tell a few of y'all are I know
they're cute and they have little fun
hands
and you see them and you go oh they're
robbing me but they they
bite and almost they have rabies all of
them they're they're actually this is
serious they are the second leading
cause of rabies in the
world that's not true but it feels right
I don't like these raccoons cute and
dangerous weird combo to me they're like
the opposite of a bosum you ever watch a
possum posum does good work dude it eats
snakes it eats ticks it can't carry
rabies but you know we're all adults
let's agree it's the ugliest thing
you've ever seen it's backwards from a
raccoon I would never say God made a
mistake but you know I'm going ask him
about it I don't know what happened that
day I want him gone so I called a friend
who knows about this stuff right I said
how do I get rid of these raccoons he
goes you trying to do it the easy way or
the hard way I was like boy I don't know
uh maybe easy just for Giggles he goes
all right all you got to do is put a
little wolf urine out
[Laughter]
there I don't know if y'all can guess
this about me by now I don't have a lot
of wolf
urine laying around the house I didn't
hunt growing up I didn't know that was a
commodity I'm like wolf you're you
telling me to hunt down a I'm terfy to
raccoons buddy you want me to pin down a
wolf and get its urine from it where you
he goes no dude just buy some I was like
oh yeah we're going to different stores
I've been shopping my whole life I've
never bumped into some wolf
urine in the checkout line where do you
get that at he goes I got a
guy well I'm going to pass on your guy
you know I've never bought wolf Ur
before I don't know if I want to buy un
regulated just handar
artisanal wolf urine from a stranger and
then I don't know what to do how do I
deploy it you want me to just walk
around my house like a
[Laughter]
priest I go I can't believe I'm saying
this what is the hard way man if the
easy way is the UR of an apex predator
what in God's name is the hard way he
goes well you know how raccoons don't
like
cucumbers uh nah I didn't know that I
haven't been hanging out with them or
anything did y'all know that about
raccoons they don't like cucumbers
that's good info what do I do with that
go to the farmers market get a big one
just wait till the sun goes down just
come out swinging
he goes no D you don't hit them with
they don't like the smell just plant
some
so that's the
Hardway start a
garden and I don't know how long it
takes cucumbers to grow but evidently
one day these raccoons will come out and
be
like you know what let's get out of here
I didn't know they were these type of
people
that's my least favorite vegetable
I go I appreciate your cander man I'm
not doing either of those Solutions is
it possible to split the difference I
know that sounds nuts but is there a a
medium difficulty solution is there
something between wolf urine and
cucumber farming is there something in
the middle that I can do he goes you got
a
crossbow I was like no I don't think so
he goes I got one I said what are you
proposing he said I'm proposing you text
me your address you cash at me 300 bucks
and you leave the house for a few hours
so so he's there right now and we will
we will see when I get home thank you
guys so much for being here I appreciate
y'all y'all are the best
[Music]